Franky J.N Lumban Gaol

Software Developer

L +6285262055720

■ 02 Jan 2000

Enthusiastic and self-motivated web designer with over 3 years of experience. Excited to join your company and bring my expertise in frontend development, and visual design to any future projects. A previous project to upgrade and redesign sbiomfs.com.au resulted in a 50% increase in web traffic and a 20% increase in performance. and Create the mobile version reference of website sbiomfs.com.au

Experience

ReactJS Developer - Pojokan.io Community

Oct 2020 - Jun 2022

- Developed responsive user interfaces using React.js, ensuring optimal performance across different devices and browsers.
- Implemented state management using Redux, enhancing the scalability and maintainability of the applications.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to plan and execute complex features and functionalities.
- Improved website accessibility by adhering to web standards and implementing WCAG guidelines.
- Developed responsive web applications using ReactJS and JavaScript for enhanced user experience.
- Collaborated with designers to convert wireframes and mockups into interactive web interfaces.
- Utilized HTML, CSS, and SASS to implement visually appealing and consistent web designs.

ReactJS Developer - PT Asuransi Astrabuana

Jun 2022 - Dec 2023

- Created responsive and user-friendly interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript(Jquery) and Wordpress.
- Developed and maintained front-end frameworks and libraries such as ReactJS.
- Collaborated with designers and back-end developers to implement seamless website experiences.
- Created Restfull Service and API using NodeJS
- created cross-browser development and responsive design

Frontend Developer - PT Smartfren Telecom Tbk

15 February 2024 - 14 Mei 2024

- Created responsive and user-friendly interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript(Jquery) and Wordpress, React native, NextJS
- Developed and maintained front-end frameworks and libraries such as ReactJS.
- Collaborated with designers and back-end developers to implement seamless website experiences.
- · created cross-browser development and responsive design

Education

SMA Negeri 2 Lubuk Pakam

Jun 2014 - Apr 2017

Social Science

STMIK Mikroskil

Aug 2017 - Dec 2021

- Bachelor of Science Information System
- GPA: 3.57

Skills

- Javascript / Typescript NodeJS
- SQL

C#

- Problem-solving
- ReactJS / NextJSAgile
- html/css AWS

Jquery

Wordpress

- Jquery
- Bootstrap, Material UI, tailwind
- axios
- Git / Bitbucket / Gitlab / Github Redux / MobX

Languages

• Indonesia | Active

• English | Conversation